CasperFlow. Build autonomous AI agents on the Casper blockchain. No code.
A built-in wiki documents every action and on-chain capability.
Organize your agents in separate workspaces,
and drag a workspace into the bar to pin it.
Build from a palette of blocks. First, triggers,
then Logic, including a Wallet that holds a real Casper key.
Choose which wallet signs. Here, Wallet 3.
Each wallet shows its real on-chain transaction history.
Connect actions like building blocks, data flows to the next step.
Casper Actions: send CSPR, stake, call contracts, anchor attestations,
real-world-asset actions,
and outputs like Telegram or Discord.
Or skip the dragging, just describe your agent in plain English.
A Treasury Guardian: read balance, decide with AI, pay, anchor the proof on-chain.
One click, the AI builds the entire flow.
Your agent is ready.
Running live on Casper testnet. Real, not simulated.
It reads the balance, the AI approves, then signs a REAL CSPR transfer.
A second AI summarizes, and the verdict is anchored on Casper (EIP-712).
Every transaction is verifiable on the public Casper explorer.
The payment, confirmed on-chain. Status: Success.
The attestation, the AI's verdict, permanently anchored. Success.
Bring your own AI model, wallets and data sources.
Integrations: Casper, AI models, Telegram, Discord,
real signing wallets, an MCP server for any AI agent, and the CSPR.trade DEX.
CasperFlow. Autonomous, verifiable AI agents on Casper.